cadbull.com 2017-06-24

# Cadbull | Privacy policy

Thank you for visiting the www.Cadbull.com. Cadbull  has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Cadbull site.

By using the Cadbull site and accepting the User Agreement you also agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you must not use the Cadbull site. This policy covers how we use your personal information.

Any personal information received will only be used to fill your order. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone.

As per the latest Privacy policy terms we have change some of rules and updated many of features in our website. We have changed the entire login panel with some of additional features which will use to every one while visiting cadbull.com 

**1.What information do we collect?**

Cadbull collects your information when you register on the Cadbull site and when you visit Cadbull pages.

Personal Information: We may collect the following types of personal information in order to provide you with the use and access to the  Cadbull site, services and tools, and for any additional purposes set out in this Privacy Policy:

Name, and contact information, such as email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, physical address, and (depending on the service used) and while you have to withdraw the money we must take financial information, such as bank account numbers.

**2.what do we offer?**

We here at cadbull lot more options of uploading a Cad-block file in cadbull.com where any user can come and sign up here for free of cost. after signing up at the Cadbull we gives you a unique id to every user and also create their profile for uploading their project so that they can recognize Their id and password  then they can can upload a cad file into our system.

While uploading a single file you will get 0.05$(USD) for each gold file upload and after then when The user reach 10$(USD) payment threshold they can withdraw their money through PayPal. We only provide PayPal payment option as per our policy standards.

  3. **How do we secure your information?**

This policy covers how we use your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information.

Do not distribute other people’s personal and confidential information, such as credit card numbers, confidential national ID numbers, or account passwords.

Any personal information received will only be used to fill your order. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone. We secure and protect Every one's Author profile in cadbull database.

  4. **File uploading guidlines**

**Spam**

Do not spam, including by sending unwanted promotional or commercial content, or unwanted or mass solicitation.

Do not aggressively send invitations, add people to your circles, or message people that you do not know.

**Use of Multiple Accounts**

Do not create or use multiple accounts to evade our policies or bypass blocks or otherwise subvert restrictions placed on your account. For example, if you’ve been blocked by another user or suspended for abuse, don’t create a replacement account that engages in similar activity.

Do not upload  any **harmful, Unauthorized, violated material ,Do not distribute sexually explicit or pornographic material.** Do not drive traffic to commercial Fake sites.

Note that your Author  profile photo cannot include mature or offensive content. For example, do not use a photo that is a close-up of a person’s buttocks or cleavage.

For breaking the File uploading Privacy Guidelines The particular user profile will be blocked and restricted for our website.  we will block that particular user profile and their information that unique id of cadbull.com never be use again to upload any project. For uploading a file every user must have to follow and Agree to our terms and condition.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at cadbull2014@gmail.com. At www.cadbull.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www..cadbull.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www..cadbull.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.cadbull.com does not use cookies. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www..cadbull.com.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www..cadbull.com and other sites on the Internet.   
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following   
URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html   
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include 

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Widget Bucks
  * Adbrite
  * Clickbank
  * Azoogle
  * Chitika
  * Linkshare
  * Amazon
  * Kontera

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www..cadbull.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.cadbull.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www..cadbull.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites
